{
    "id": "ce69f7aa67034da2a5c15da275e797e6",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Turn Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The music is too loud. Please turn it .....................",
            "description": "To turn down is to lower the volume. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "down",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6840cf7f9b304b5789a4ecbc1755645a"
        },
        {
            "question": "My application was turned ......................... because I didn't have the required qualifications.",
            "description": "To turn down an application is to reject it. ",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "199c21ec47e34e52a86bb0af4283af5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are required to turn ....................... the report within a couple of days.",
            "description": "To turn in a report is to submit it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1dddf677534347a1b32aeb4875473772"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am too tired to stay up. I think I should turn ..................... now",
            "description": "To turn in is to go to bed. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1b2ea05cb5624046968001de99a9d86e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He turns .................. a monster after he has had a couple of drinks.",
            "description": "Turn into can mean transform. ",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9b0adc5feefb4ac6b3c8542279f0f7be"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't forget to turn ..................... the fan and the lights before you leave the room.",
            "description": "To turn a device off is to stop it from working. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "away",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7e984a7bf07d4d26a7d5d491ef42f0ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had invited Samuel to my party but he didn't turn ..................",
            "description": "To turn out is to attend an event. ",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "92416bd9c6034d92ad73462343f8a374"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hadn't seen him for years. Then one day he turned .................. at my door.",
            "description": "When someone turns up, they come unexpectedly. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "82e8f735a2ce44f6ab2a2ed1d2ecbed4"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are not happy with the service you receive, you should take it .................... with the manager.",
            "description": "To take something up with somebody is to complain to them about a problem. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb2cca8350494fb7b09770fb667b0996"
        },
        {
            "question": "I may take ..................... gardening after I retire.",
            "description": "To take up something is to start doing it regularly. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c273e8759e3e4716866d32e0326ae3b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I took my wife and children ...................... to dinner yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3219e7393a3b422690921a60ca4d7c5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Germany will take .................... Argentina in the first semifinal on Friday.",
            "description": "To take on somebody is to compete against them. ",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "893a9544d3614a6db221805577d3bb13"
        }
    ]
}